<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<posts>
  <row Id="1" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="925" CreationDate="2010-07-09T19:07:45.460" Score="59" ViewCount="30457" Body="&lt;p&gt;My chocolate chips cookies are always too crisp. How can I get chewy cookies, like those of Starbucks?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Thank you to everyone who has answered. So far the tip that had the biggest impact was to chill and rest the dough, however I also increased the brown sugar ratio and increased a bit the butter. Also adding maple syrup helped. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="16" LastEditorUserId="41" LastEditDate="2011-08-22T23:44:41.317" LastActivityDate="2018-04-17T23:46:34.353" Title="How can I get chewy chocolate chip cookies?" Tags="&lt;baking&gt;&lt;cookies&gt;&lt;texture&gt;" AnswerCount="11" CommentCount="5" FavoriteCount="23" />

  <row Id="2" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="26" CreationDate="2010-07-09T19:08:34.570" Score="29" ViewCount="116927" Body="&lt;p&gt;I've heard of people cooking bacon in an oven by laying the strips out on a cookie sheet. When using this method, how long should I cook the bacon for, and at what temperature?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="17" LastEditorUserId="41" LastEditDate="2010-11-10T04:44:49.043" LastActivityDate="2015-10-06T21:04:10.933" Title="How should I cook bacon in an oven?" Tags="&lt;oven&gt;&lt;cooking-time&gt;&lt;bacon&gt;" AnswerCount="14" CommentCount="3" FavoriteCount="5" />

  <row Id="3" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="25" CreationDate="2010-07-09T19:08:47.673" Score="65" ViewCount="8278" Body="&lt;p&gt;I always use brown extra large eggs, but I can't honestly say why I do this other than habit at this point. Are there any distinct advantages or disadvantages like flavor, shelf life, etc?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="14" LastEditorUserId="1672" LastEditDate="2013-03-24T21:42:44.057" LastActivityDate="2014-02-27T17:52:57.573" Title="What is the difference between white and brown eggs?" Tags="&lt;eggs&gt;" AnswerCount="4" CommentCount="1" FavoriteCount="2" />

  <row Id="4" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="13" CreationDate="2010-07-09T19:09:20.653" Score="44" ViewCount="9154" Body="&lt;p&gt;And can I use one in place of the other in certain recipes?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="24" LastEditorUserId="20413" LastEditDate="2018-10-22T13:22:55.450" LastActivityDate="2018-10-22T13:22:55.450" Title="What is the difference between baking soda and baking powder?" Tags="&lt;substitutions&gt;&lt;baking-soda&gt;&lt;baking-powder&gt;" AnswerCount="4" CommentCount="0" FavoriteCount="6" />

  <row Id="5" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="4122" CreationDate="2010-07-09T19:09:59.187" Score="61" ViewCount="428427" Body="&lt;p&gt;It seems that every time I make a tomato sauce for pasta, the sauce is a little bit too acid for my taste. I've tried using sugar or sodium bicarbonate, but I'm not satisfied with the results.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="21" LastEditorUserId="41" LastEditDate="2010-10-14T14:52:44.257" LastActivityDate="2015-09-09T14:52:50.480" Title="In a tomato sauce recipe, how can I cut the acidity?" Tags="&lt;sauce&gt;&lt;pasta&gt;&lt;tomatoes&gt;&lt;italian-cuisine&gt;" AnswerCount="26" CommentCount="1" FavoriteCount="15" />

  <row Id="4122" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2010-07-09T19:10:15.223" Score="13" ViewCount="30113" Body="&lt;p&gt;I have a recipe that calls for fresh parsley. I have substituted other fresh herbs for their dried equivalents but I don't have fresh or dried parsley. Is there something else (ex another dried herb) that I can use instead of parsley?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I know it is used mainly for looks rather than taste but I have a pasta recipe that calls for 2 tablespoons of parsley in the sauce and then another 2 tablespoons on top when it is done. I know the parsley on top is more for looks but there must be something about the taste otherwise it would call for parsley within the sauce as well.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I would especially like to hear about substitutes available in Southeast Asia and other parts of the world where the obvious answers (such as cilantro) are not widely available.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="27" LastEditorUserId="41" LastEditDate="2011-08-22T23:41:52.213" LastActivityDate="2011-08-22T23:41:52.213" Title="What ingredients (available in specific regions) can I substitute for parsley?" Tags="&lt;substitutions&gt;&lt;herbs&gt;&lt;parsley&gt;" AnswerCount="8" CommentCount="3" FavoriteCount="0" />

  <row Id="13" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2010-07-09T19:10:53.503" Score="29" ViewCount="181343" Body="&lt;p&gt;I'd like to know when to take my steaks off the grill and please everybody.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="18" LastEditorUserId="1443" LastEditDate="2010-07-31T06:49:19.133" LastActivityDate="2014-07-21T07:42:26.040" Title="What is the internal temperature a steak should be cooked to for Rare/Medium Rare/Medium/Well?" Tags="&lt;food-safety&gt;&lt;beef&gt;&lt;cooking-time&gt;" AnswerCount="3" CommentCount="0" FavoriteCount="5" />

  <row Id="25" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2010-07-09T19:12:05.017" Score="60" ViewCount="5288" Body="&lt;p&gt;What's the best method to poach an egg without it turning into an eggy soupy mess?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="29" LastEditorUserId="4638" LastEditDate="2018-10-18T09:24:53.257" LastActivityDate="2018-10-18T09:24:53.257" Title="How should I poach an egg?" Tags="&lt;eggs&gt;&lt;poaching&gt;" AnswerCount="13" CommentCount="0" FavoriteCount="16" />

  <row Id="26" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2010-07-09T19:12:12.223" Score="23" ViewCount="5482" Body="&lt;p&gt;My ice cream doesn't feel creamy enough.  I got the recipe from Good Eats, and I can't tell if it's just the recipe or maybe that I'm just not getting my &quot;batter&quot; cold enough before I try to make it (I let it chill overnight in the refrigerator, but it doesn't always come out of the machine looking like &quot;soft serve&quot; as he said on the show - it's usually a little thinner).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Recipe: &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.foodnetwork.com/recipes/alton-brown/serious-vanilla-ice-cream-recipe/index.html&quot;&gt;http://www.foodnetwork.com/recipes/alton-brown/serious-vanilla-ice-cream-recipe/index.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Thanks!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="26" LastEditorUserId="1887" LastEditDate="2011-03-22T20:21:22.900" LastActivityDate="2014-08-08T20:15:48.693" Title="How can I make my Ice Cream &quot;creamier&quot;" Tags="&lt;ice-cream&gt;" AnswerCount="9" CommentCount="0" FavoriteCount="1" />

  <row Id="925" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="4" CreationDate="2010-07-09T19:12:25.373" Score="26" Body="&lt;p&gt;Normal double-acting baking powder makes CO2 (thus giving a rising effect) in two ways: when it gets wet, and when it is heated.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Baking soda only makes CO2 when it gets wet.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Baking_powder&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noreferrer&quot;&gt;From Wikipedia&lt;/a&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;  &lt;p&gt;The acid in a baking powder can be&#xA;  either fast-acting or slow-acting.[6]&#xA;  A fast-acting acid reacts in a wet&#xA;  mixture with baking soda at room&#xA;  temperature, and a slow-acting acid&#xA;  will not react until heated in an&#xA;  oven. Baking powders that contain both&#xA;  fast- and slow-acting acids are double&#xA;  acting; those that contain only one&#xA;  acid are single acting. By providing a&#xA;  second rise in the oven, double-acting&#xA;  baking powders increase the&#xA;  reliability of baked goods by&#xA;  rendering the time elapsed between&#xA;  mixing and baking less critical, and&#xA;  this is the type most widely available&#xA;  to consumers today. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="31" LastEditorUserId="3987" LastEditDate="2018-10-22T00:00:51.517" LastActivityDate="2018-10-22T00:00:51.517" CommentCount="2" />
</posts>
